That was a blessing. Uh I'm uh um happy
that you all are joining us uh today. We
are uh going to be getting into the word
of God at this time. And uh as I stated
earlier, uh I am
I'm really excited about this message.
Um I think God has something very
important that he wants to share uh with
his people. And um we're going to just
we're going to have a word of prayer and
then we are going to jump into the
message. Uh I hope that you have your
Bibles uh because we are going to be uh
we're going to be going deep into the
word of God this morning. So uh with
that said, let's pray uh and let's
begin. And heavenly father,
we um just take this time Lord to
present uh our hearts to you. Um asking
Lord that you would please speak to us
Lord that you would um
encourage us, strengthen us,
Lord, that you would be truthful
with our condition.
Lord, help us to see our great need,
which is Christ,
which is the word of God.
So bless us now, Lord, as we open your
word. And we pray this in the name of
Jesus. Amen. Amen.
The title of my message
is social distancing, the three angels
message and the right arm of the gospel.
Social distancing, the three angels
messages and the right arm of the
gospel.
Um
we are living in a time that is unlike
anything we have seen in our lifetime
and um
I think that as a people many of us are
waking up to certain realities.
uh if this is indeed
um
a
a snapshot of what it will be like in
the time of trouble.
Would we be ready? I think that's a
question that a lot of people are
asking. Would we be ready? And I think
some people are answering that question.
Yes. Uh I would personally be ready. And
others are saying no. I find myself
unprepared.
But I want to speak to you today about
about
something very very specific
and and it deals with the last part of
my title, the the the right arm of the
gospel.
Because
God has given this church
a health message.
And
more than ever before,
we need to be living up to that health
message.
I I hope you you can give me a hearty
amen to that because
that's what I'm going to be talking
about today. Now, don't tune out. Please
don't don't say to yourself, "Oh, I know
the health message, so uh this message
is not for me." Just please hold on. We
are living in a time right now where we
have something that is precious to the
world,
but also precious to ourselves. If there
was ever a time that we should be
keeping the health message, that we
should be living up to the health
message, that time is now.
All right, I want you to just keep that
in the back of your mind. And I'm going
to we're going to go to our first
scripture.
Uh I want to invite you to look with me
in the book of Psalm 33 and verse one.
And I'm just going to go ahead and
forewarn you that uh you're probably not
going to uh uh
why are we talking about Psalm 33:1 when
pastor is talking about the health
message? I just want you to follow along
and pay very close attention. Okay. So,
Psalm 33:1, the Bible tells us there,
"Behold, how good and pleasant it is for
brethren to dwell together in unity."
Right now we are going through this
social distancing
uh um
crisis if you will
and
it's very opposite of what Psalm 33:1 is
talking about right I can imagine that
many of us are probably thinking back
two 3 weeks ago and remembering
uh that it wasn't so bad meeting in
church after all right Uh the Bible
tells us how good and pleasant it is for
brethren to dwell together in unity.
Listen carefully.
The purpose of the church. The purpose
of the church. The church was raised up
for the purpose of unity.
I'm going to say that again. The church
was raised up for the purpose of unity.
It was raised up to be united and to
unite. I want you to notice what John
chapter 10 verse 16 and 17 says. John
chapter 10:16 rather Jesus speaking says
other sheep have I which are not of this
fold. Them also must I bring and they
shall hear my voice and there shall be
what? One fold and one
shepherd.
Jesus wanted unity for his church. He
wanted his church to be so close. Listen
carefully. He wanted his church to be so
close together that they were that they
would be considered one.
Now,
we're in a situation right now where we
can't meet together as we used to,
right? We've got this social social
distancing thing going on. But I think
it's a perfect time to talk about the
importance of unity in God's church. But
let's keep building the foundation. I
want you to notice with me Ephesians
chapter 4. Ephesians chapter 4 verse
one. The Bible says, "I therefore the
prison of the Lord beseech you that you
walk worthy of the vocation wherewith
you are called with all loneliness and
meekness, with longsuffering, forbearing
one another in love, endeavoring to keep
the unity
of the spirit in the bond of peace.
There is what? One body and one spirit.
Even as you are called in one hope for
our for your calling, one Lord, one
faith, one baptism, one God and father
of all who is above all and through all
and in you all. So you see here this
emphasis on unity in the church. The
Bible says that we were to strive
endeavor to keep the unity of the
spirit.
Let me go ahead and take you over to
John chapter 17.
Jesus
said these words, I am now I now am no
more in the world, but these are in the
world. And I am come to thee, holy
father, keep through thine own name
those whom thou has given me that they
may be what? One. That they may be one
as we are one.
Jesus wanted unity for the church in
John 17 21 that these may all be one as
thou father art in me and I in thee that
thou may also be one in us that the
world may believe that thou hast sent me
and the glory which thou gavest me I
have given to them that they may be what
one even as we are one I in them and
thou in me that they may be made perfect
in one listen carefully that the world
may know that thou hast sent me and has
loved them and as thou hast loved them.
So we're just building a foundation here
and seeing how important oneness, unity,
a closeness in the church of God.
Closeness,
right? So close that we will be
considered one.
That's crazy, right? In this time of
social distancing, I want you to notice
what I'm talking about. God desires a
unity for his church
that basically makes them so close that
they are one.
Notice Romans 12:4. For as we have many
members in one body, and all members not
have not the same office, so we being
many are one body in Christ. and
everyone members of one another. So now
what we're seeing here is that the the
the members of the church actually make
up the body of Christ. All right? So
please follow what I'm saying here
because this is this is very important
extremely important. God desires unity
in his church. unity among the members.
A unity that is so powerful,
so close that they would be considered
one. Now that one unity may be
summarized as the body of Christ, the
body of Christ. Okay? God desires for
his body to be one. So now I just want
you to imagine the church as the body of
Christ, right? the head, arms, torso,
legs, feet. The church, the members of
the church are to be so closely united
that they form one body which is the
body of Christ.
What is the purpose of the body?
So that's my question for you. What is
the purpose of the body especially in
these last days? Let me share with you
Revelation 14, a verse that you should
all be familiar with. The Bible says,
Revelation 14:6, "And I saw another
angel fly in the midst of heaven, having
the everlasting gospel to preach unto
them that dwell on the earth, and to
every nation, kindred, tongue, and
people,
saying with a loud voice, "Fear God, and
give glory to him, for the hour of his
judgment is come, and worship him that
made heaven, the earth, the sea, and the
fountains of waters." So the purpose of
the unity, the purpose of the oneness of
the body is to take the gospel into all
the world.
If you're following so far, um just a a
a thumbs up, a a heart, a amen,
something. Okay. The purpose of the body
of Christ is to take the gospel into all
the world. Now what is the purpose of
the gospel? By the way,
the power of the body of Christ is in
its unity
because unity signifies love.
So therefore, the more united we are,
the more powerful
the message we take to the world. the
everlasting gospel. Now, why are we
taking the everlasting gospel to the
world? Well, Jesus summed it up in Luke
4:18. Notice what he says there. The
spirit of the Lord is upon me because he
has anointed me to preach the gospel to
who? The poor. And I want you to notice
this next phrase. He has sent me to
heal.
He has sent me to heal. Heal the
brokenhearted. to preach deliverance to
the captives and recovering of sight to
the blind, to set at liberty them that
are bruised. In other words, guys,
listen carefully. The gospel
heals.
I want you to catch that.
The gospel is designed to heal us from
the wounds of sin. We have a message to
take to the world. That message is taken
to the world through the body of Christ
which whose power is through its unity.
And the message we have is a healing
message.
A healing message. Now let me ask a
question. How many of you
um
would
uh I can't even ask a question yet
because I'm just going to give it away.
Let me just say it this way. The power
of the message of God's people depends
upon the unity of God's people. the the
the
social closeness,
not the social the social closeness of
God's people determines the power
whereby we take the gospel into the into
the whole world. Now remember, we're
taking the gospel into the world because
that gospel is a healing message. And in
fact, one of our favorite verses about
God's end time movement is found in
Isaiah 58:12. And here's what it says.
And they that shall be of thee shall
build the old wasteplaces. Thou shalt
raise up the foundations of many
generations, and thou shalt be called
the repairer of the breach, the restorer
of paths to dwell in. That's what the
gospel is all about. It's about
repairing the breach. It's about
bringing wholeness. It's about bringing
healing to sin sick souls. We are called
to be repairers of the breach. We love
this verse. Isaiah 58:12. How many of
you love this verse? Raise your hand in
your homes. I know we can't see you, but
just amen. I love that verse.
But there's something that happens
before that verse.
You see, Isaiah 58 is not a very
flattering chapter for us. I want you to
notice this. Check this out. In Isaiah
58, verse 8, look at what the Bible
says. Okay? I hope you're sitting down.
I hope you are I hope you're about to
catch what I'm about to tell you.
Because in Isaiah 58, the Bible says
here in the same promise for God's end
time people, you know, the repairs of
the breach, it says, "Then shall thy
light break forth." Now, pause for a
second. Then, well, whatever that then
is, it means something is going to
happen. That then
shall our light break forth as the
morning, and thine health shall spring
forth speedily, and thy righteousness
shall go before thee, and the glory of
the Lord shall be thy reward. Rear
reward. Now, I have a question for you.
If your health has to spring forth, what
does that indicate? Remember, we're
talking about God's end time people, the
repairers of the breach, right? Those
who are going to take the message uh to
the whole world at the end of time, they
are going to be called repairers of the
breach. But just a few verses up, we
read that at some point, this group of
people, their light will spring forth
and their health shall spring forth
speedily.
What does that mean?
If I am healthy, then there's no need
for my health to spring forth speedily.
I hope I hope you catch what I just
said.
The only reason I would want my health
to spring forth speedily is if I'm sick.
What is God trying to say to us? Listen
carefully.
The people of Isaiah 58, the repairs of
the breach who are supposed to go forth
with this end time message, repairing
the breach, restoring the past of
dwelling. God says that at some point
this body,
the health of this body is going to
spring forth. Meaning the body prior to
this time
was experiencing
sickness.
Oh,
wait a minute. Sick
us the body. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're the remnant. What are you talking
about sick? Well, God said it right
here.
God says that at some point the church's
health will spring forth speedily,
indicating that before this point, the
church is unhealthy. And I'm asking you
today, do you are you beginning to to
understand what I'm saying? Because what
the Bible is telling us is this. Listen
carefully. If we are supposed to be
going forward to the world with a
message of healing, how can we have any
effectiveness in preaching that message
if the body itself is sick?
How can we go forward with a message of
healing if the church itself is sick?
Our health needs to spring forth
speedily before we become repairers of
the breach.
Are you catching what I'm saying?
So, I know what you're asking right now.
Wait a minute. Is the body sick? Like,
what are you talking about? Remember,
listen carefully. Remember the strength
of the body
is the unity within the body.
A unified body is a strong and healthy
body.
Oh boy.
A unified body, a body which
endeavors to keep the bond of peace, of
love. A unified body is a healthy body.
It's a body that can go forth in power
bringing a message to the world of
healing. Why? Because the body itself is
healthy.
The church itself is healthy.
However, if the
if the body becomes compromised,
let me ask you this. Speaking about your
personal health, what is the thing that
you want to take care of the most? What
is the thing that defends your body?
It's called your what? Your what system?
Is called your immune system, right?
Your immune system is what keeps the
body healthy. Healthy immune system,
healthy body.
Not so healthy immune system, not so
All right, guys. I need you to check
this out.
Notice with me in Acts chapter 20, verse
29.
How many of you know what the killer tea
cells are? Yes. Yes. Yes. You know what
those are, right? Killer tea cells are
part of the immune system whose purpose
it is to identify, isolate, and destroy
foreign invaders into the body. So, how
many of you praise God that we are
fearfully and wonderfully made? Amen.
That's right. We're fearfully and
wonderfully made. Yes. Praise God. And
God has given us an immune system. And
beloved, it's the same for the church
body. The church body was given an
immune system. I hope you are following
me here.
The church body in order to remain
healthy had to be given an immune
system. And I want you to check it out.
The immune system
was designed to watch for invaders into
the body that could cause pathogens and
cause h of foreign things to come into
the body that would cause the body to be
sick. So for example in the book of acts
20 28 Paul says these words take heed
therefore unto yourselves watch
for the body. Take heed therefore unto
yourself and to all the flock over the
which the Holy Ghost has made you
overseers to feed the church of God
which he has purchased with his own
blood. For I know this that after my
departing shall grievous wolves enter in
among you not sparing the flock. Also of
your own selves shall men arise speaking
perverse things to draw away disciples
after them. Pause for a second. Was Paul
here warning that there were going to be
invaders in the body of Christ? Yes, he
was. And what he was saying was, I need
you to be the immune system. I need you
to look out for for false things that
will come into the body and compromise
the health of the body. Listen, church,
we have a health message. And now more
than ever, we need to be living by that
health message. I hope you're catching
what I'm saying.
So Paul said, "Listen, I need you to be
vigilant." You know what? There's
nothing more
there's nothing more amazing than an
immune system that works effectively.
Paul said, "I need you to look out for
the body because Satan is going to try
to make the body sick." And if the body
becomes sick, it's going to be
ineffective in doing what the body has
been called to do, which is to go
out into the world and preach the
everlasting gospel to all the world, a
gospel of healing.
All right.
So check it out. What were these people
going to do who entered into the flock?
They would seek to draw away or let me
put it this way. They would seek to draw
away people from Christ. Or let me
rephrase it this way. They would seek to
create
social
distancing
from Jesus
and ultimately from the body of Christ.
Division.
If the strength of the body is unity,
if the strength of the body is unity,
the strength of the body of Christ,
then Satan understands that the way to
weaken the body of Christ,
come on guys,
is to create social
or spiritual
distancing
from Jesus Christ.
Because once we begin to distance
ourselves from Jesus Christ, we also
begin to distance ourselves from one
another.
All right? I hope you're catching this
guys. Check this out. Once again, 2
Timothy chapter 4 verse one. I charge
thee before God and the Lord Jesus
Christ whom who shall judge the quick
and the dead at his appearing in his
kingdom. Preach the word. Be instant in
season and out of season. Reprove,
rebuke, exhort with all longsuffering
and doctrine. Why? For the time will
come that they will not endure sound
doctrine, but after their own, lust
shall they heap to themselves teachers
having itching ears. You get the idea.
Paul is saying, listen, I need you to be
the immune system
for the body.
I need you. Everybody,
everybody who is a part of the body of
Christ should be looking out for the
health and the well-being of the body of
Christ. Beloved, we have a health
message and now more than ever, we ought
to be living up to that health message.
So, you're saying, "Pastor, what are you
trying to say here?" Well, listen
carefully what I'm trying to say because
did you know that the immune system can
actually malfunction?
[Music]
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. The immune system
can actually malfunction. What do you
mean? It can either become hypervigilant
or it can become dormant.
Listen. When the immune system becomes
overactive, it attacks the body. It is
unable to differentiate between foreign
invaders and the body itself. Listen
carefully guys. Its fear of infection
leads it to destroy the body. Let me say
it this way. Its overzealous desire for
purity and wholeness blinds it to the
body and it begins to divide and to
isolate that which should not be divided
and isolated.
Are you catching what I'm saying?
Could it be that the enemy of souls
seeks to weaken the body
by causing the immune system of the body
to become overactive?
Pastor, what do you mean? Come with me.
Isaiah 58,
same chapter, right? I want you to
notice what Isaiah 58 says. It says,
"Cry aloud, spare not, lift up thy voice
like a trumpet, and show my people their
transgression and the house of Jacob
their sin." This is the same chapter,
Isaiah 58, that ends with, "They shall
be called repairs of the breach." It
begins with show my people their sins.
You can't be a repairer of the breach.
You got to first recognize your sins.
You got to first recognize there's
something you're doing that is bringing
sickness in the body.
Does Isaiah 58 go on to tell us what
that is? Yes, it does. Guys, please
listen carefully. Isaiah 58:3,
"Wherefore have we fasted, say they, and
thou seeest not. Wherefore have we
afflicted our soul, and thou takest no
knowledge? Behold, in the day of your
fasting, you fast for pleasure and exact
all your labors. Notice verse four.
But you fast for what?
You fast for strife and debate and to
smite the fist of wickedness.
What is God saying here?
You You are not seeking unity in the
body. You are seeking strife. You are
seeking debate. The body is experiencing
division.
You can't be a repairer of the breach
until you first recognize the division
happening in the body.
I I am speaking as straight as I can
right now. Le let let's go a little
further. Let's check out verse 9 because
the Bible says verse 9, remember this.
Bible is saying in Isaiah 58, these are
the things you're doing, but if you
change, then
you will be pure repairs of the breach.
Then your light will spring forth. Then
your health will spring forth. What are
we talking about? The health of the body
of the church.
God is telling us we're sick right now.
How do we know we're sick? Because
there's division happening in the body.
The immune system of the body is not
operating correctly. Remember, there are
two things that can happen with the
immune system. It can either become
overzealous
or it can become inactive.
H
inactive means, hey, we're going to let
whatever into the body. Overzealous
means everything is evil. You know where
those cameras came from?
Yeah. Yeah. Have you heard about the TVs
lately? Everything becomes evil.
And beloved, either one of these
approaches makes the body sick
because it brings in division and strife
and and and and and h a suspicion and
all kinds of things designed to make the
body weak. If there is no immune system,
sickness enters the body. And when
you're sick, you don't feel like going
into all the world.
H check this out. I Isaiah 58:9. I
didn't even read the text. Listen what
it says. Then shalt thou call, and the
Lord shall answer. Thou shalt cry, and
he shall say, "Here I am." Listen
carefully. "If you take away from the
midst of thee the yoke, and the putting
forth of the finger," pause for a
second.
What do you think it means putting forth
of the finger?
What's God saying here?
You guys need to stop putting forth the
finger. What does that What do you think
that means? You I'm sure you're getting
this right now. What does putting forth
the finger mean?
You're pointing.
Look at what so and so is doing. Look at
what that one. You become an accuser of
the bre. That's what putting forth of
the finger means. It means accusing the
brethren.
You get to the place where in the church
of God, people are so busy accusing one
another in the name of the immune system
that the body begins to become sick and
cannot accomplish its mission. After
all, how can we go out there and tell
the world about a message of healing
when the body itself is sick?
[Music]
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You need to see this.
You're saying, "Pastor, where is this?
What? Tell me about this division. I I
don't need to tell you, but let's talk
about it." Right?
If
think about how much division happen is
happening in our church right now over
doctrinal issues.
Come on man.
I just want you to think about that.
Right? Just think about uh what is your
interpretation of prophecy and what is
your interpretation of oh that
interpretation of prophecy where you
think uh the king of the south is this
power versus this power. You're an
apostasy. You're evil. You're a tear.
And that's what happens. Like we don't
know
how to disagree without being
disagreeable.
We don't know how to disagree over a
subject. What do you believe about this
issue? What do you believe about that
issue? We you take a side and you are
the apostate.
Beloved, listen to me. We need to learn
how
to disagree with a position
without demonizing other people.
Because when we make other people the
enemy, the immune system is attacking
the wrong thing.
We're attacking
the a part of the body versus dealing
with the issue that is coming into the
body.
It's okay to disagree. I'm not saying
that everyone, you know, has to believe
this way about, you know, the book of
Revelation or the book of Daniel or this
or that or what. It's okay to have a
difference of opinion and that opinion
may be totally wrong.
But beloved, if we don't know how to
love each other
in spite of our differences,
we are being hypocritical about this
message of healing that we're talking
about.
See, not only doctrinal issues, not only
uh uh uh you know, mundane issues,
issues that shouldn't be dividing at
all. What about hate in the church? What
about racism in the church?
Didn't think I was going to say, did
you? Yes. I say, "What about racism in
the church?" Listen to me, beloved.
There are a lot of people in the church
who are racist and don't even know it.
Peter was a racist and didn't even know
it.
And guys, listen. You don't have to be
one color to be racist.
There is racism happening in a lot of
different ways in the church.
Underhanded racism. And listen,
that's why the Bible says, "Search your
heart, Lord. Search my heart and sh
what's in my heart." Cuz sometimes you
don't even know what's in your heart.
And beloved, these things are causing
division in the church. The most obvious
one, what are you? Conservative. What
are you, liberal? You're a liberal,
you're an you're an apostate. You're
conservative, you're an apostate. And so
what do we do? We socially distance.
Beloved, Satan is trying Satan has had
us socially distancing before it became
a thing to be so to practice social
distancing. We've been social
distancing.
What do you believe? All right. We're
not going to invite you to our church to
speak.
ministries
that are supposed to be reflecting the
unity of Christ and underhandedly. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. No, we're not inviting that
person. No, we're not inviting that
person.
You guys really
really
if the leaders of the church
can't demonstrate true love and
brotherly sisterly courtesy,
how are the how are the members of the
church going to follow? How are they
going to rise any higher
if ministries are vying for oh who's
better and who's better and yeah when I
invite them and guys I'm going to tell
you this is happening in ministries this
is happening in ministries all over it's
hypocritical
I'm not saying you know again I'm not
saying you have to uh agree with it I'm
simply saying I'm simply saying that if
we don't know how to love one another if
we don't know how to guard one another's
reputations even if we believe listen I
have a a I have a dear f I have dear
friends who who you know have gone off
into some things and you know what I'm
I'm a public figure I could have easily
gone on Facebook and been like yep boom
boom boom boom boom and you know nopem
no you want to know why cuz those are my
friends and if I'm going to correct
them. I'm going to correct them
privately.
I'm going to talk to them privately
because I wouldn't do that if it was my
brother. If it was my mother or father,
if they were doing I wouldn't be going
and, you know, blasting them. And guess
what? We in these days, we have no
qualms about getting on Facebook,
getting on social media and airing just
how sick the body of Christ is, the
church. You understand what I mean when
I say the body of Christ?
Peter
social distancing.
Yeah, you remember Galatians 2:11. Paul
says, "But when Peter was come to
Antioch, I withtood him to his face
because he was to be blamed. For before
that certain ca certain came from James.
He did eat with Gentiles. But when they
were come, he withdrew and separated
himself, fearing them which were of the
circumcision." You know how it is. You
don't want to hang out with certain
people because you're afraid what other
people might say. Even though you might
like that person, you just don't want to
be seen around them or connect with them
or have your ministry connect with them
because what might your followers or
your supporters of your ministry say? If
we have produced an atmosphere, an
environment of social distancing that is
sickening the body of Christ and we need
to stop it. Now, don't get me wrong,
guys. I'm not talking about the social
distancing that we have to do now on a
physical level. That's not I'm talking
about social distancing on a spiritual
level. We are separating and remember
the the power of the body of Christ is
in its unity. But if we continue this
social distancing, you know, between
black adventism and white Adventism and
conservative and liberal and are you a
Republican or are you a Democrat and how
could you and all this stuff going on,
what ends up happening, beloved, is that
we become so sick that we cannot
accomplish our mission
because everybody becomes suspect. We're
turning on everybody. Yep. He's suspect.
She's suspect. They're suspect. And only
the people that I'm cool with are
really, really, really doing the Lord's
work.
You see where this go? Where this is
going?
So
in one instance, the immune system
becomes overactive.
Everything is wrong. Everything is evil.
Everyone is evil.
And only you or only your ministry or
only your church or only your group of
friends only you are the ones that have
not bowed the knee to bail.
That's a hyper that's that those are
signs of a hyperimmune system that is
actually destroying the body. you can no
longer differentiate between the body
and the actual illness entering into the
body.
On the other hand, you have the failure
of the immune system which says, "Hey,
whatever goes,
so it doesn't matter. We can't get sick.
Body of Christ is cool. So, whatever
goes goes." Beloved, neither of those is
healthy. When the body is sick, the
gospel cannot go forth with power. How
can it? How can we call others to unity
when we're not experiencing unity in the
church ourselves?
How can we bring a message of healing
when we are still sick?
But God has not left the church without
hope.
If anyone knows how to heal, it's the
Adventist church. Like, somebody needs
to say amen to that.
If anyone knows the secret to building a
healthy immune system, a healthy body,
if anyone knows how to combat disease,
it's the Adventist church. And why do I
say that? Because you know it, guys. We
listen, we need a new start.
We got a health message, don't we? We
have a health message that can heal. So
if we have a health message that can
heal and the body is sick, man,
why don't we just apply the health
message to the body
so that we can get healed and we can
have a new start? How many of you would
like a new start?
I think so. I think you're looking for a
new start. I think you see the church
needs a new start. I think you see that
there is so much division and animosity.
And you know what? A lot of you are
disappointed that the GC is not
happening this year because you were
looking forward to a good fight.
Yes, you were, weren't you? You were
just waiting to see what's going to
happen at the GC this year. You were
looking for the fight.
You guys, this is just a sign of how
sick the body has become and how much we
need to be healed. So, we have what's
called new start. You know what it is,
right? Nutrition, exercise, water. Huh?
Come on, you fill it in. What else?
Sunshine, temperance, fresh air, rest,
and trust in God. So, let's go through
it. We just we're just going to see how
can we apply the health how can we as a
church begin to practice the health
message. Well, let's start with
nutrition, guys. Nutrition, nutrition,
nutrition. If you want a healthy immune
system to protect the body of Christ,
it's all about nutrition. Man shall not
live by bread alone, but by every word
that proceeds out of the mouth of God.
Beloved, we need to take the word of God
seriously. We need to stop putting the
word of God on the shelf. We need to
take the word of God seriously because
in the word of God are lifegiving
nutrients that are going to help the
body become better. Help the body heal
because the body can heal itself. All
you have to do is give it the right
fuel. And for many of us, we're not
giving it the right fuel. We're eating
junk food. We're not eating the word of
God.
So God is telling us, listen, if you
want to be repairs of the breach and and
have your health spring forth, you need
to stop fighting among yourselves and
you need to start getting into the word
of God. Amen.
The word of God is it's all about
nutrition. Second Peter 1:19. We also
have a more sure word of prophecy where
unto you do well that you take heed as
unto a light that shineth in a dark
place until the day dawn and the day
star rise in your heart. We have
prophecy that we could be eating, guys.
It's a sweet book.
Nutrition, nutrition, nutrition. We got
to start getting to the word of God. We
got to stop taking it light. We got to
stop, you know, like just wanting
messages that make us feel good about
ourselves. We need, listen, especially
now, we need to be getting deeper into
the prophecy so we can understand, you
know, I know there's so many of us that
don't even know like, are we in the end
time? What's going on? I have no clue.
What what is it saying in Revelation? We
shouldn't be acting like this. Of all
the people on the planet, we should be
the ones that are like, "Look, here's
where we are in the book of Revelation.
Here's what's coming." But the fact that
so many of us are asking the question,
it is this the abomination of desolation
standing in the is it reveals
why we are sick.
Nutrition, nutrition, nutrition. Guys, 2
Timothy 2:15, "Study to show thyself
approved unto God, a workman that
needeth not be ashamed, rightly dividing
the word of truth." And beloved, listen
to me. Uh uh nutrition. Yes, nutrition.
Eat the word. But you know what?
We are we are very close to the end,
guys. And I would say that there's only
so much you could eat at one time. So,
I'm going to suggest juicing the word.
Yes. Yeah. We need to juice the word.
When you're really sick and you really
need that dose, juice the word.
Yes.
Take in more than you normally would
because it's going to bring healing.
It's going to give you strength and
power. Okay. So, that's nutrition. What
about the next one? E for exercise.
Exercise, guys. We need to start
exercising.
Second Timoth or 1 Timothy 4:7 says,
"Refuse profane and old wise fables and
exercise thyself rather unto godliness."
Guys, we need to start exercising
exercising godliness instead of pointing
fingers and instead of looking at
everyone as the enemy and instead of uh
uh doing the stuff that's bringing about
sickness and disease, let's start
learning how to exercise godliness. Not
just talk about it, but actually
exercise it. Look at what God says in
Jeremiah 9:24. But let him that glorieth
glory in this in this that he understand
this and knoweth me that I am the Lord
which exercises loving kindness. Guys,
let's start exercising loving kindness.
Right? Exercising loving kindness to
those who may not be so kind back to us.
Let's start exercising loving kindness
and and and and righteous judgment, not
selfish judgment and righteousness in
the earth because that's what God
exercises.
Let's learn. Let's get let's let's get
up and start move in godliness,
right? How about Hebrews 12:1? Hebrews
12:1 talks about weightlifting. Yeah,
weightlifting. Weightlifting is a good
exercise. So, so it says here,
"Wherefore, seeing we are all so
compassed about with so great a cloud of
witnesses, let us lay aside every
weight." Oo, come on, somebody.
Let Let's lay aside that. Let's Let's
Let's learn how to move weight, the
weight that so easily besets us.
Let's learn how to run a little bit.
Let's Let's go running. Let's go jog
every day. run that race. Lift that
weight.
God is calling us to get on a weight
loss program. Yeah, you need to lose
some weight. Uh yes, I said it. You need
to lose some weight. Why? Because many
of us are carrying around the weight of
unforgiveness, the weight of bitterness,
the weight of jealousy, the weight of of
of suspicion. That's what we're doing.
So, we're so heavy that we can't
exercise. We can't run the race.
because we're busy looking at everybody
else.
Guys, listen to me.
Like, I've experienced this, okay? So,
I have been here.
It's easy to look at what others are
doing and say, "Oh, yeah, evil." And,
"Oh, yeah, evil." And, "Oh, yeah, evil."
It's easy to do that. It's not so easy
to look at yourself.
God is saying you be your own immune
system. Look at yourself. Let the others
worry about them. Let them worry. Every
man work out their trembling, their
salvation with trembling and fear. And
if you're going to try to help somebody
else, try to help them. Not condemn them
or hate them, but try to help them. What
they may be doing may be totally wrong.
That's not the argument I'm presenting
here, right? I'm not saying like, hey,
it doesn't matter. I'm just simply
saying we need to learn how to handle
our differences. We need to learn how to
handle when someone doesn't believe as
we do.
We need to learn how to love those who
may who we may disagree with on certain
doctrines.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Beloved, we need to learn
how to exercise. Okay. Not only there's
there's there's there's nutrition,
there's exercise, and there's also
water, right? Water. The W in new start.
Water. Why is water get plenty of water?
That's a that's a known health principle
for us. Genesis or Acts chapter 3:19
tells us this. Repent ye therefore and
be converted that your sins may be
blotted out when the time of what?
Refreshing
shall come from the presence of the
Lord. This was the outpouring of the
Holy Spirit symbolized as the outpouring
of the latter rain.
The reason why water is so important,
beloved, is because it helps us to
hydrate. And many of us are dehydrated.
We don't have no spirit in us.
No spirit. We're dehydrated. You need
that water of the spirit. You need that
outpouring of the spirit in your life so
that it'll hydrate your cells and you'll
be filled with the spirit.
Galatians 5:16 says this. This I say
then, walk in the spirit. Walk in the
water you have taken in and you shall
not fulfill the lust of the flesh. It
goes on to say the fruit of the spirit
is love, joy, peace, longsuffering,
gentleness, goodness, faith, meekness,
temperance. Beloved, in order for fruit
to grow, there has to be water.
You got to water the fruit. Hydrate,
drink that water, and the fruit of the
spirit will be the result. And then you
can exercise that fruit of the spirit on
people that you disagree with
so that we won't have division in the
body that causes it to be weak.
Not only is water used for the purpose
of hydrating, we got a whole bunch of
dehydrated Christians because they are
not saturated with the Holy Spirit.
They're not hydrated with the spirit.
But listen,
water is also used to purify.
Now, we ought to know this, right? If
the church wants to be healthy, if you
want to avoid viruses getting into the
body, wash your hands.
I'm just getting excited. Wash your
hands.
James chapter 4:8 says this,
"Draw nigh to God and he will draw nigh
to you. Cleanse your hands, you sinners,
and purify your heart." You wash your
hands because you know the hands are one
of the most uh uh uh efficient ways to
spread viruses.
Wash your hands.
Make sure you have clean hands.
He's saying, "Pastor, clean hands."
Expound. Well, listen. In Isaiah 59:2,
the Bible says, "But your iniquities
have separated between you and your God,
and your sins have hid his face from you
that he will not hear. For your hands
are defiled with blood, and your hands
are defiled with blood, and your fingers
with iniquity, your lips have spoken
lies, and your tongue has muttered
perverse things." They go together, hand
and tongue.
So God says, "Your hands are full of
blood." Well, I've never killed anyone.
Oh, wait a minute. Whosoever hates his
brother is a murderer. Oh man, I just
need to like spin in my chair or
something.
If you hate someone,
okay? And you know, sometimes I hear
people say, "I don't hate you. I just
don't like you." Which means I hate you.
Don't don't don't be cute with it. Don't
be cute with I don't like you.
And the Bible says if you hate your
brother, you have blood on your hands.
Your hands are filthy. Your hands are
not clean. And what's happening is,
listen carefully, you are you are
spreading disease in the body because
you go and use those bloody hands and
shake someone else's hand and that
person's like, "Yeah, I don't like that
person either." And then they go and
what happens is instead of going to one
person only, the person you may have an
issue with and and isolating, did you
hear what I said? Isolating. socially
isolating that virus so that it's just
between you and the individual. Matthew
18, go to that individual alone. No, no,
no, no, no. You go and go infect someone
else and someone else and someone else.
And what happens is that this pandemic
of hate,
this pandemic of suspicion, this
pandemic of of I don't like you just
spread through the church. You heard
what pastor so and so said. You heard
what Elder so and so said. You heard
what they said at the GC. You heard what
this ministry and this pandemic spreads
to where everybody almost everyone is
infected.
H
infected with the virus
of hate.
Yeah. Proverbs 17:9. He that coverth a
transgression seeks love, but he that
repeatth a matter separates friends,
causes social distancing.
This is how people spread. This is how
viruses of hate and jealousy spread.
When you carry that virus of hate and
you don't wash your hands and wash them
frequently,
wash your hands, guys.
That's water. Wash your hands.
Okay. Sunshine. We know that the health
message tells us we need to get plenty
of sunshine. Mhm. We need to just bask
in the sun. Are you catching what I'm
saying? We need to bask in the sun.
Yeah. Malachi 4:2 tells us that. But
unto you that fear my name shall the son
of righteousness arise with healing in
his wings, and he shall go forth, and
you shall go forth and grow up as calves
in the stall. You need to get some Get
out, man. Get some sun.
Don't be a pale Christian.
Get some sun.
Because when you get sun, listen,
listen, listen what the Bible says about
the son. You have heard that it's been
said, "Thou shalt love thy neighbor and
hate thine enemy." But I say unto you,
"Love your enemies.
Bless them that curse you. Do good to
them that hate you. Pray for them which
despitefully use you and persecute you,
that you may be the children of your
father which is in heaven. For he makes
his son to rise on the evil and on the
good and sendeth rain on the just and
get some sun because when you get some
sun, you can give others sun, right? You
can be sunshine to others instead of
being darkness to them. Instead of I
hate you, you can be sunshine. Listen,
man. I don't agree with your theology,
but I love you as a brother, and I will
pray with you, and I will love you. I
don't agree with your stance on this or
your stance on that, man. Listen to me.
Like, do you know how much division is
being caused by people just I don't like
the way you interpreted that scripture
or I don't even like the way you study
the Bible. I don't like the way you
preach your sermon. So, we're not going
to invite you because I didn't see what
you saw in that sermon. So, you know
what? Yeah. We're just not gonna Yeah.
You guys come on. Seriously.
Seriously.
We are not the Holy Spirit.
Let your sunshine. The Bible says, "Let
your light so shine that others may see
your your good works and glorify your
father in heaven." Get out into the sun.
That's going to help the body become
healthy. Okay. So, we got nutrition,
exercise, water, we got sunshine. Uh uh
what about temperance?
Temperance. That's self-control.
What What does God want us to control?
He wants us to control the tongue. That
he says you control the tongue, you can
control everything else. James 1:26, if
a man among you seem to be religious and
bridleth not his tongue, but deceives
his own heart, that man's religion is
vain. So just as in the literal uh uh
issue of temperance, we're trying to
control what we eat and not eat so much,
not overeat. In the spiritual context,
we need temperance. Control your tongue.
Stop gossiping.
Stop talking about people.
Stop repeating. Stop spreading. Stop
those things. Control your tongue.
Because what's happening is you when you
control your tongue, the virus can't
spread in the body.
But no, no, no, no. What we do is we go
out into the gossip stores. Hey yo,
guess what? And we just poison people
against people. That's all we're doing.
And the virus just spreads and spreads
and spreads.
You control the tongue. and the virus.
At least you do your part in helping to
kill a virus. The virus of sin.
All right. So, we got temperance. What's
the What's next? We got air. Fresh air.
We have to get lots of air, guys.
We need fresh wind. Fresh air. John 3:8,
the Bible says, "The wind bloweth where
it listeth, and thou hearest the sound
thereof, but cannot tell when it cometh,
and whether it goes." So is everyone
that is born of the spirit.
Beloved,
we need the fresh air of the Holy
Spirit. We are told that prayer is the
breath of the soul. I think my Instagram
feed I just died. So if you're on
Instagram, I apologize. Uh maybe we'll
see if we can get it get it started up
again. Listen,
prayer is the breath of the soul.
If we don't know how to pray together,
don't expect to be healed together.
There's a re the way you can tell the
church is sick is just look at our
prayer meetings.
Just look at our prayer meetings.
The lungs of the church are almost they
are filled with with with sickly fluid.
So we don't even pray together.
We just, hey, I'm not go. No pray. No.
Why not? Because I don't like that
person or just cuz I'm just too busy to
pray.
We need fresh air. Look at our prayer
meetings and you can tell that the virus
of social distancing is attacking the
lungs and robbing it of much needed air.
You guys, we need sunshine. We need
temperance. We need air. And listen
carefully. You know what comes next,
right? Rest.
We need rest. Get some rest, guys. Get
lots of rest. If I could encourage you
to do one thing above every other, it
would be get lots of rest. And the
question is, how does the body get rest?
Jesus told us in Matthew 11:28, "Come
unto me all come unto me all ye that
labor and are heavy laden, and I will
give you what?" rest. Yes. Take my yoke
upon you and learn of me, for I am meek
and lowly, and you shall find rest for
your souls. Do you know that the body
heals itself when it's getting rest?
The body heals itself when it's getting
rest. So Jesus tells us, if you want to
get healed, you need to rest. How do we
rest, Lord? Come to me. Come to you. We
I don't get it. What does that mean?
Listen. Check this out.
Listen to this statement, guys.
The cause of division and discord in
families and in the church is I'm going
to change this word here, social
distancing from Christ.
Watch this. To come near to Christ
is to come near to one another.
The secret of true unity in the church
and in the family is not diplomacy, not
management, not a superhuman effort to
overcome difficulties, though there will
be much of this to do. So, we're not
minimizing there's going to be work and
it's going to be a challenge,
but the true answer is union with
Christ. And now check out this example
that is used. Picture a large circle
from the edge of which are many lines
all running to the center.
The narrower these lines approach the
center, the narrower they are to one
another. Thus it is in the Christian
life, the closer we come to Christ, the
narrower we shall be to one another. God
is glorified as his people unite in
harmonious action. Do you catch this?
Rest means coming to Christ. The closer
we come to Christ, the closer we come to
each other. We're not fighting each
other. We're coming close to Christ. And
we begin to unify.
That's what it means to rest, you guys.
And finally, trust. Trust in God. Trust
that God has his church under control.
Trust him and obey him. Isaiah 12:2,
"Behold, God is my salvation. I will
trust and not be afraid. For the Lord
Jehovah is my strength and my song. He
also is become my salvation. Beloved, if
we do these things, we can rebuild a
healthy immune system. One that is not
overactive, one that is not inactive,
but one that will allow the body to be
one. And when the body is one, we can go
and complete the mission that God has
called. We can then become repairers of
the breach. You guys, we have a health
message. We need to follow it.
We need to follow it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You may be following it on a personal
level for your physical health, but as a
church body, we need a new start. We
need a reset. And the health message is
the answer. Huh? Who would have thought?
All right, guys. Listen, I I need to
share this with you, okay? Because you
see, many of us, here's what you're
saying right now. You're saying,
"Listen, I don't want to be around this
person or that person because I am
fearful of being contaminated by them."
That should not be a fear of yours in
the church. Here's why.
Because God has instructed us to wear
protective gear.
Yes.
Yes. Yes. God has given us protective
gear that if we wear it, we don't have
to worry about contamination
by coming into contact
with others who may not be serious about
following God at that point in their
walk. You say, "Pastor, what's that
protective gear?" Listen carefully.
Finally, my brethren, be strong in the
Lord and in the power of his might. Put
on the whole armor of God that you may
be able to stand against the ws of the
devil. For we wrestle not against flesh
and flesh and blood, but against
principalities, against powers, against
the rulers of the darkness of this
world, against spiritual wickedness in
high places. Wherefore take unto you the
whole armor of God, that you may be able
be able to stand uh in the evil day, and
having done all to stand, stand
therefore with your loins gout with
truth, and having on the breastplate of
righteousness, and your feet shaw with
the preparation of the gospel of peace,
and above all taking the shield of
faith, wherewith you shall be able to
quench all the fiery viruses of the
wicked,
and take
your N95 mask of salvation.
All right, it doesn't say that. But take
the helmet of salvation that's going to
protect your head. That's going to
protect any virus from entering into
your eyes or your nose or your mouth.
It's going to protect you. Take that and
and the sword of the spirit, which is
the word of God, praying with all prayer
and supplication. God says, "I am giving
you
so much protection that you will not
need to fear." If we're afraid to go
around people, if we're afraid to be,
it's because we're not wearing the
armor, we're not wearing the protective
gear. Now, I'm about to wrap this up,
but this is Listen, what I'm about to
share is the most important thing that
I've shared thus far in this message.
And I need you to listen closely.
I need you to listen carefully
because God's trying to heal us so that
we can do something mighty. And if we're
not healed, we're not going to be able
to do what God has called us to do. So
the good news is we're going to be
healed because the Bible prophesies it.
The question is, will you be a part of
the body when it's healed or will you be
somewhere outside the body? Will you be
one of those viruses end up being so
connected with a virus that when the
time for the body is totally healed, you
have been removed from the body? Check
this out, guys. Isaiah 40:31, a text we
all know and love. They that wait upon
the Lord shall do what?
Renew their strength. Guys, I'll be done
in five minutes. Okay, so just I don't
even know how long I've been preaching.
I think I got caught up in what I was
saying, but just give me five more
minutes. Okay.
They that wait upon the Lord shall renew
their strength. They shall mount up with
wings as eagles. They shall run and not
be weary. They shall walk and not f.
This verse is talking about healing.
They that wait upon the Lord shall renew
their strength. The sick are weak.
God says
they that wait upon the Lord shall renew
their strength. And when their strength
is renewed, what are they going to do?
They're going to mount up with wings as
eagles. That's powerful, guys. You need
to catch this.
If they are sick,
they have no strength. And if they have
no strength, they can't mount up.
All right, pastor. Where you going with
this? Listen, that word, but they that
the term but they that wait, listen to
how Strong's concordance describes this
word. It means it's a primitive root
which means to bind together
to bind together perhaps by twisting
that is to collect figuratively to
expect to gather together to look
patiently tarry wait so the reason it
doesn't say but he that waits on the
Lord it says but they that wait on the
Lord in other words they're waiting
Together
they are moving together. They that
together wait upon the Lord shall renew
their strength. The secret to the
renewing of their strength is that
they're doing it together.
Wait, wait, wait. That same word is used
in Genesis 1:9. First time it's used.
And God said, "Let let the waters under
the heavens be gathered." same same
Hebrew word be gathered
together unto one place and let the dry
land appear and it was so. So the word
means together
they that together wait upon the Lord.
What's going to happen to them? They're
going to renew their strength. And when
they renew their strength, they mount up
with wings. Like where do they mount up
to? According to the book of Ephesians
chapter 2:4, the Bible says, "But God,
who is rich in mercy, for his great love
worthy loved us, even when we were dead
in sins, has he quickened together with
Christ. By grace are you saved, listen
carefully. And has raised us up together
and made us sit together in heavenly
places in Christ Jesus."
How do they get up there?
With eagle's wings.
They get up there because they mount up.
They waited on the Lord.
And when we do this together as a body,
we're invited into heavenly places.
Watch this, guys. Listen carefully.
The key to flight,
to being able to remain in heavenly
places is unity.
I hope you're catching this, guys.
The key to flight,
to mounting up with wings like eagles,
is unity. It has to be done together.
It has to be done together.
Remember in Revelation 12:14
how the woman in the dark ages, remember
that woman? Remember her? What does the
Bible say about her? Come on, let's
look. Let's look. It says to the woman
were given two wings of a great eagle
that she might fly into the wilderness
into her place where she is nourished
for a time times and half a time from
the face of the serpent. Even though the
woman in the dark ages, even though
Satan was trying to scatter her, listen
carefully, she was given wings of an
eagle because the church of the dark
ages, the woman of the dark ages was a
united church.
That's why she could mount up with wings
like eagles.
They were united in the Lord.
The power of flight lay in the degree of
unity in the church. Now, I got a
question for you that I actually never
asked myself until today, until last
night when I was putting this together.
And here's a question.
What happened
to that woman?
Right? Obviously, that woman in in that
time period is is no longer here. That
was the dark ages. But what ultimately
happened with that woman, right? We look
at that woman and we say that woman
represents the church of the dark ages.
It represents the Protestant
Reformation. But check this out. What
happened? What began to happen in the
Protestant Reformation?
Did they begin to divide? Did they begin
to practice social distancing?
I'm just going to wait.
You see, once Satan could get into the
church and start to divide them. Oh
yeah, we believe this. Oh yeah, you
believe that. Oh, you believe that. You
believe. And once these divisions
started happening, that became the basis
for the multiplication. Listen
carefully, the multiplication of all
these churches which are now known as
mystery Babylon
because they never completed a
reformation. Why? Because division began
to rise inside these very movements.
Pastor,
where are you going with this? You guys
need to see this.
In Isaiah 58:14, the Bible says, listen
carefully. That same chapter we began
with Isaiah 58, right? Listen. Then
shalt thou delight thyself in the Lord.
When you when you are healed, when all
these things happen, you do this the
right way. When you stop fighting, when
you stop dividing, then shalt delight
yourself in the Lord. And I watch this
guys who I will cause thee to ride upon
the high places of the earth. What do
you think he means when he says ride
upon the high places of the earth? Well,
let me just share with you. He uses the
same word. The same word is used in
Psalm 18:10. And he that is God rode
upon a cherub and did fly. Yay, he did
fly upon the wings of the wind. So what
does it mean to ride upon the high
places? It means to mount up with wings
like eagles.
So now he's telling us when we are
united, when we stop fighting, you're
going to have power to mount up. To
mount up where? To mount up into heaven.
Why do we need to mount up into heaven?
Listen guys, to fly, you have to wait on
the Lord.
Meaning the church must be unified.
Meaning the church must be healthy in
order to fly. Why am I talking about
flying? Why? Why? Why? Why am I talking
about Why am I talking about the church?
Listen guys, in Revelation 14:6, the
Bible says, "I saw another angel fly.
Fly in the midst of heaven.
having the everlasting gospel to preach
unto them that dwell on every on the
earth, to every nation, kindred, tongue,
and people. Listen guys, we're not
flying. If we are sick,
we're not strong enough to mount up and
to actually fly in the heavens as the
prophecy states, so that we can finish
the work.
Because to fly represents swiftness,
to fly represents a a a quick work.
But something's happening.
I I I can't say that we're flying.
Have we yet mounted up? Have we yet are
we riding up on the high places?
Yeah, the gospel is going forth.
But beloved, we could be doing this much
faster if the church was actually
healthy.
We could actually mount up like w like
eagles. mount up on eagle's wings and
finish the gospel rapidly.
But we're sick.
And if we're sick, we can't really mount
up and fly the way God wants us to fly.
It's time to abide by the health
message, guys.
That's my appeal to you. You want to
fly? Do you want to fly?
The church in the dark ages had wings.
We need wings, too. Because that angel
doesn't represent a real angel flying
in. It represents the people of God.
They are the ones that are flying. The
church of God, the body of Christ, they
are the ones that are flying. So, if we
want to fly, we got to mount up with
wings like eagles. But if we want to
mount it with wings like if we want to
mount up on wings like eagles, we have
to do it unitedly.
And unity is the strength of the body of
Christ. Division is the weakness of the
body of Christ.
So you can either be a part of the
problem or you can be a part of the
solution.
We need to pray. Lord,
help us to get rid of this division.
Help us to get rid of this division.
Help us to get rid of the racism in this
church. Help us to get rid of the
division. Help us to get rid of the
sides. Help us to get rid of the teams.
Help us to get rid of everything that
separates us. And it's hard because I
know you got people looking at you and
and and if you try to make that first
step to be the one that says, "Hey,
I'mma reach my hand across and let you
know you Yeah. Others are going to look
at you like, "What? You you did what?
You hung out with who?"
Guys, let's abolish social distancing in
the church. You get what I'm saying?
Let's abolish this attitude of
separation within amongst ourselves. And
if we do that right, the gospel will go
around the world rapidly and the end
will come. If that's your desire,
I'm just going to ask you to say amen,
to lift your hands, to do whatever you
need to do to say, Lord, that's me.
That's me.
Help me, Lord. no longer to be a part
of. Help me not to spread these viruses
going around in the church. Help me to
just help me to just nope not spreading
it. I'll wash my hands. I'll abide by
the health message. I will do everything
I need to do to cause the virus of
separation and jealousy
and hatred and anger in the church to
die. Because when it does, we can be
about our father's business. We can go
back to work. We can go back to work. I
want to go back to work. The church
needs to get back to work. We do. We do.
Let's do it, guys. Jackie, please lead
us.
[Music]
I'll come back after you and pray.
Brother,
[Music]
there's much
kindness.
We can the darkness
as he shines.
We will come
[Music]
with a song of healing.
And they will
[Music]
change
it around.
Let it never leave.
And they will know us by
the time
[Music]
church
around
it.
And they will know
[Music]
as we um as we prepare to pray.
Uh, I want you to realize something.
[Music]
If the body of Christ is sick,
the people that we try to go to,
they see that sickness
and they stay away from the body.
Nobody wants to be around somebody
that's sick.
When we go out into the world and we
present the gospel, but people are
saying, "Wait a minute, your church is
sick."
What's the message we're sending?
Let's get healed.
Let's learn to love one another.
[Music]
And then they will know us by our love.
Heavenly Father,
we thank you for speaking to us.
Lord, we pray that you forgive us for
ignoring the very message you gave us to
give us good health.
in ignoring that message, in ignoring
nutrition and in ignoring exercise and
water and and and and sunshine and
temperance and air and rest and trusting
God and in ignoring these things, Lord,
we have compromised the immune system
and allowed sickness to enter the body
causing division.
Now Lord, we have prayed for
forgiveness. We're now asking that as a
body you would help us to adopt the
health message that we may have a new
start
that we may reset.
[Music]
Bring healing to the body Lord.
Remove everything that is unlike you.
And most of all, Lord, we pray that you
would bring unity into the body of
Christ.
May that unity lead to our strength and
lead to us mounting up into heavenly
places that we may fly unimpeded
around this world to spread
the three angels messages.
Grant us our wings, Lord, that we may
finish the work.
[Music]
Thank you Lord for being merciful to us.
Fill us with your presence as our prayer
in Jesus name. Amen. And amen.
[Music]